excuse us uh we're closing up now what
pardoner brunch service ends at 3: do
you have any idea who I am Wendy Sean
Aspen brocken your names are not on this
list in fact all the names are crossed
out cuz brunch is over I just want you
to understand that I could buy and sell
you like the movie Taken with lurm nurer
do you want to be a white slave cuz it's
a lot of
sex how about we just go get a duffel
bag full of carsh and buy this
place big money big
so we're calling the restaurant dunch we
were going to call it lunch like El
apostrophe unch like late Branch look I
don't care what you call the restaurant
all right as long as I control the food
I love how shiny you are I have a
spinach puree that I serve with a red
wine that's a Cabernet that gives you
the feeling that you're on a white
waterer rafting trip with all your high
school friends and you have this feeling
like man I should I should do more stuff
with these guys cuz they're they're
close to me we'd like this restaurant to
be sort of like farmed a table so that
we can get like someone fist like waen
farx and he sits at one of our tables my
kitchen my rules darl you're hard who's
Daryl I thought am I hired or is so what
was your vision in her obviously the
signature piece to our dining experience
is the fiberglass table with the teen
runaway just living her life e she's
well fed all of our waitresses are
biracial a lot of them are half Jewish
because I'm transitioning to Judaism so
the theme is not not no food no no
that's not the play at all there should
be food hold on a
second I just didn't know if you guys
were doing some sort of like Shia slf
Franco SL Nomi thing where people come
expecting food but instead they get
inconvenienced hold on childood friend
happening look what's happening I'm
walking childood friend T just wait just
let me talk to the sharp let me talk to
the sharp Aspen all the taste makers are
leaving hey teen runaway use your
Connections in the freight Community to
find out where our f is you're trash
you're garbage you're white trash what
are you going to do just go eat dinner
nothing's open except for dunch there's
a certain kind of trouble that only
grows under the one1 overpass after it's
rained yesterday it rained so today I
had to track down a pig to help me track
down the troubles dunch is getting
dumped in the dirt uh calm down our
childhood friend Terrence left he's not
impressed at all and everyone is leaving
all because Mr Bobby fle over here
decided to go out for a walk looking for
mushrooms oh there's no way you're
Grilling and Chilling as cool as my man
B F Well I take that as a compliment
okay Rachel
Ray Rachel Ray oh I'm Rachel Ray now huh
I'm Rachel Ray I'm Rachel
[Applause]
[Music]
Ray